{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Drywall Installation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40030/":{"taskOID":40030,"originalTaskOID":40030,"setID":354,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5480,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of drywall project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6042,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard drywall installation (hang, tape, sand, and texture)","answerDisplayText":"Standard drywall installation (hang, tape, sand, and texture)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3238,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install (hang) drywall only","answerDisplayText":"Install (hang) drywall only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3258,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install moisture proof drywall (green board)","answerDisplayText":"Install moisture proof drywall (green board)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3240,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Install Wonderboard or Durarock (backer board for tile)","answerDisplayText":"Install Wonderboard or Durarock (backer board for tile)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6255,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tape and sand joints only","answerDisplayText":"Tape and sand joints only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6256,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tape, sand, and texture only","answerDisplayText":"Tape, sand, and texture only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5974,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Spray texture only","answerDisplayText":"Spray texture only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5282,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Replace popcorn acoustic ceiling spray with texture to match walls","answerDisplayText":"Replace popcorn acoustic ceiling spray with texture to match walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5216,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms for Drywall Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which rooms of your house need drywall? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2241,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Entry","answerDisplayText":"Entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1303,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Ceiling(s) only","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling(s) only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6031,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Stairwells","answerDisplayText":"Stairwells","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2724,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Garage or storage room","answerDisplayText":"Garage or storage room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5481,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Finish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of finish(es) do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No finish","answerDisplayText":"No finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2467,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fire tape only (garage, storage, work room)","answerDisplayText":"Fire tape only (garage, storage, work room)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5829,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Smooth finish (no texture) to paint","answerDisplayText":"Smooth finish (no texture) to paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5832,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Smooth finish to apply wallpaper/faux painting techniques","answerDisplayText":"Smooth finish to apply wallpaper/faux painting techniques","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5707,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Simple texture (orange peel, knockdown)","answerDisplayText":"Simple texture (orange peel, knockdown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1538,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complex texture (hand troweled)","answerDisplayText":"Complex texture (hand troweled)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6304,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Texture to match existing drywall","answerDisplayText":"Texture to match existing drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7124,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would also like paint","answerDisplayText":"Would also like paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5480,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of drywall project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6042,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard drywall installation (hang, tape, sand, and texture)","answerDisplayText":"Standard drywall installation (hang, tape, sand, and texture)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3238,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install (hang) drywall only","answerDisplayText":"Install (hang) drywall only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3258,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install moisture proof drywall (green board)","answerDisplayText":"Install moisture proof drywall (green board)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3240,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Install Wonderboard or Durarock (backer board for tile)","answerDisplayText":"Install Wonderboard or Durarock (backer board for tile)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6255,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tape and sand joints only","answerDisplayText":"Tape and sand joints only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6256,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tape, sand, and texture only","answerDisplayText":"Tape, sand, and texture only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5974,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Spray texture only","answerDisplayText":"Spray texture only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5282,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Replace popcorn acoustic ceiling spray with texture to match walls","answerDisplayText":"Replace popcorn acoustic ceiling spray with texture to match walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6042,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard drywall installation (hang, tape, sand, and texture)","answerDisplayText":"Standard drywall installation (hang, tape, sand, and texture)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3238,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install (hang) drywall only","answerDisplayText":"Install (hang) drywall only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3258,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install moisture proof drywall (green board)","answerDisplayText":"Install moisture proof drywall (green board)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3240,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Install Wonderboard or Durarock (backer board for tile)","answerDisplayText":"Install Wonderboard or Durarock (backer board for tile)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6255,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tape and sand joints only","answerDisplayText":"Tape and sand joints only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6256,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tape, sand, and texture only","answerDisplayText":"Tape, sand, and texture only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5974,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Spray texture only","answerDisplayText":"Spray texture only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5282,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Replace popcorn acoustic ceiling spray with texture to match walls","answerDisplayText":"Replace popcorn acoustic ceiling spray with texture to match walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5216,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms for Drywall Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which rooms of your house need drywall? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2241,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Entry","answerDisplayText":"Entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1303,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Ceiling(s) only","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling(s) only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6031,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Stairwells","answerDisplayText":"Stairwells","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2724,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Garage or storage room","answerDisplayText":"Garage or storage room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2241,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Entry","answerDisplayText":"Entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1303,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Ceiling(s) only","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling(s) only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6031,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Stairwells","answerDisplayText":"Stairwells","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2724,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Garage or storage room","answerDisplayText":"Garage or storage room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5481,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Finish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of finish(es) do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No finish","answerDisplayText":"No finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2467,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fire tape only (garage, storage, work room)","answerDisplayText":"Fire tape only (garage, storage, work room)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5829,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Smooth finish (no texture) to paint","answerDisplayText":"Smooth finish (no texture) to paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5832,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Smooth finish to apply wallpaper/faux painting techniques","answerDisplayText":"Smooth finish to apply wallpaper/faux painting techniques","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5707,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Simple texture (orange peel, knockdown)","answerDisplayText":"Simple texture (orange peel, knockdown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1538,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complex texture (hand troweled)","answerDisplayText":"Complex texture (hand troweled)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6304,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Texture to match existing drywall","answerDisplayText":"Texture to match existing drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7124,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would also like paint","answerDisplayText":"Would also like paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No finish","answerDisplayText":"No finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2467,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fire tape only (garage, storage, work room)","answerDisplayText":"Fire tape only (garage, storage, work room)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5829,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Smooth finish (no texture) to paint","answerDisplayText":"Smooth finish (no texture) to paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5832,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Smooth finish to apply wallpaper/faux painting techniques","answerDisplayText":"Smooth finish to apply wallpaper/faux painting techniques","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5707,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Simple texture (orange peel, knockdown)","answerDisplayText":"Simple texture (orange peel, knockdown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1538,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complex texture (hand troweled)","answerDisplayText":"Complex texture (hand troweled)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6304,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Texture to match existing drywall","answerDisplayText":"Texture to match existing drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7124,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would also like paint","answerDisplayText":"Would also like paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40030/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40030,"taskName":"Drywall - Install","taskDescription":"Install Drywall","xmTaskDescriptor":"Drywall Installation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":2801,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"dry wall drywall remodeling construction","textMessagingName":"Install Drywall","rolloverLongDesc":"Not for repairs.  Specialist who hangs (nails or screws) drywall \u0026 fills \u0026 smoothes the joints in remodeling or construction.   For plaster on lath work, see specific work category.","rolloverShortDesc":"Also called plasterboard, sheetrock \u0026 gypsum.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Drywall.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Drywall Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Drywall Hangers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":59,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Drywall Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Drywall - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Drywall Project","urlName":"Drywall-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Drywall Installers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"dry,wall,drywall,remodeling,construction, wall,sheetrock,hang,gypsum,board,wallboard, plasterboard,skim,coat, dry wall, ceiling","emcCategoryOid":-12025,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":354,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}